Finding Aid for Joseph Beal Steere Papers 1861-1941
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence with Family and Friends 1861-1926
  - Mary (J.B. Steere's daughter)
    - 1922, 1923, 1924, 3 letters (Box 4)
April 6, 1877; March 14, 1888; August 25, October 1.December 24, 1890; May 7, 1894; March 3, 1898
Senier, Alfred, d. 1918.
October 20, 1876
Sharpe, Richard Bowdler
Sept. 12, 1876; Sept. 16, 1889; Sept. 15, 1891; Nov. 14, Dec. 21, 1895
Shufeldt, Robert W. (Robert Wilson), 1850-
May 17, June 1, 1894; Apr. 24, May 21, 1907; Mar. 22, 1908; Jan. 19, 1909
Steere, Isaac.
January 19, 1897
Van Deman, Henry Elias, 1845-1915.
May 13, 1887
Wallace, Alfred Russel, 1823-1913
August 30, 1876
Ward, Henry A. (Henry Augustus), 1834-1906.
June 20, 1887
Waterhouse, Frederick Herschel
February 20, August 26, 1891
Whitman, Charles Otis, 1842-1910.
Undated
Wilder, Burt Green, 1841-1925.
June 9, 1897
Wilson, Robert.
December 31, 1873
Winchell, Alexander, 1824-1891.
June 12, July 29, 1869; June 13, 1870; April 2, 1872
Wood, W. W.
October 4, 1874
Woolridge, C. W.
April 14, 1884
Selective Index to Correspondents: 1984 accession of papers
Angell, James Burrill, 1829-1916.
March 20, May 8, 1873
Bartlett, Harley Harris, 1886-1960.
February 9, 1932 (re: Joseph B. Steere birthday)
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.
September 7, 1923
Blair, William McCormick, 1884-
November 15, 1927 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Brigham, Edward Morris
November 28, 1933 (re: Amazon studies, etc.)
Brightman, Edgar Sheffield, 1884-1953.
March 9, 1930 (re: Joseph B. Steere argument for teleology.)
Case, E. C. (Ermine Cowles), b. 1871.
November 30, 1927 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Chapman, Howard Rufus, 1868-1942.
March 29, 1924 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Cooley, Charles Horton, 1864-1929.
November 27, 1927 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Dewey, John, 1859-1952.
November 7, 1929 (re: Joseph B. Steere manuscript on religion and evolution.)
Fairchild, David, 1869-1954.
May 11, 1898 (asking opinion about annexing/colonizing Philippines and developing its agriculture.)
Ferguson, Alfred Lynn, b. 1884
February 7, 1927 (re: article on faith)
Frieze, Henry S. (Henry Simmons), 1817-1889.
June 27, July 26, August 17, October 8, 18, 1871; January 28, March 18, 1872
Harrington, Mark Walrod, 1848-1926.
March 24, 187?, June 29, August 24, 1871; September 19, 1872; March 15, 20, August 5, 7 (2), 23, September 20 (?), October 1, 1873; May 6, July 13, 1874; August 1, December 18, 1875
Henderson, William D., b. 1866.
February 6, 1928 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Hinsdale, W. B. (Wilbert B.), 1851-1944.
November 22, 1927
Jackson, Walter Hinckley, 1840-1930.
February 14, 1924 (on religion)
Johnston, Clarence Thomas, 1872-1970.
March 15, 1920; May 3, 1924 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith); November 25, 1927
Leete, Frederick Deland, 1866-1958.
February 20 (re: religion), March 8, May 20, 1929; January 26, 1935 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on age)
Phelps, William Henry, 1872-1939.
October 23, 1928 (re: draft of Joseph B. Steere book on evolution and religion)
Roth, Filibert, 1858-1925.
February 21, 1924 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
November 23, 1929; April 29, 1932; January 19, 1935; February 9, 1940
Steere, Joseph Hall, 1852-1936.
March 6, 1924 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith); January 10, 1927 (Joseph B. Steere Children's Stories.); November 10, 1927 (Joseph B. Steere article on evolution), December 8, 1927; March 18, 1932
Wenley, R. M. (Robert Mark), 1861-1929.
October 28, 1928 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Wilgus, Horace L. (Horace La Fayette), 1859-1935.
October 31, 1927 (re: Joseph B. Steere article on faith)
Winchell, Alexander, 1824-1891.
March 187?, October 8, 187?, January 8, June 27, December 10, 1871; January 10, 28, April 10, August 27, October 1872, November 12, 1872; February 6, 1877